{
    "subject": "resource/Fabula_Nova_Crystallis_Final_Fantasy",
    "predicate": "property/platforms",
    "object": "resource/PlayStation_3",
    "human_readable": "Fabula Nova Crystallis Final Fantasy is available on PlayStation 3.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9714019894599915,
            "question": "Is Fabula Nova Crystallis Final Fantasy a PlayStation game?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9484239816665649,
            "question": "Besides PlayStation, are there other platforms where Fabula Nova Crystallis Final Fantasy is available?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9465619325637817,
            "question": "On what platform is Fabula Nova Crystallis Final Fantasy available?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9151903986930847,
            "question": "What console can you play Fabula Nova Crystallis Final Fantasy on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9029137492179871,
            "question": "Which generation of PlayStation consoles supports Fabula Nova Crystallis Final Fantasy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.87489914894104,
            "question": "What type of game is Fabula Nova Crystallis Final Fantasy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8275667428970337,
            "question": "What is the name of the video game franchise that includes Fabula Nova Crystallis Final Fantasy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8045312762260437,
            "question": "What year was Fabula Nova Crystallis Final Fantasy released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8000330328941345,
            "question": "Does Fabula Nova Crystallis Final Fantasy have online multiplayer capabilities?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.710006594657898,
            "question": "Is Fabula Nova Crystallis a PlayStation exclusive title?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Fabula Nova Crystallis Final Fantasy is available on PlayStation 3.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4644_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Fabula Nova Crystallis Final Fantasy have online multiplayer capabilities?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4644_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was Fabula Nova Crystallis Final Fantasy released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4644_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the video game franchise that includes Fabula Nova Crystallis Final Fantasy?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4644_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4644_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4644_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4644_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4644_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4644_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4644_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4644_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4644_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4644_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4644_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\n**Explanation:** The documents provide information about the release of multiple titles under the \"Fabula Nova Crystallis\" project, including for the PlayStation 3 platform. For example, \"Final Fantasy XIII\" is mentioned as being available on the PlayStation 3, and other titles like \"Versus XIII\" are also noted to be developed for the PS3 system. Therefore, the statement that \"Fabula Nova Crystallis Final Fantasy is available on PlayStation 3\" is supported by the given context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}